knowledgesocialnetwork.com 2011-11-26

# Privacy | knowledgeSocialNetwork

**Privacy Statement**

This site is owned and operated by KnowledgeSocialNetwork – KnowledgeSocialNetwork.com. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At KnowledgeSocialNetwork, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

For the purpose of this privacy policy, “you” and “your” refers to any visitor of KnowledgeSocialNetwork, “users” and “user” refers to a registered readers or authors of KnowledgeSocialNetwork, “member” or “members” refers to a registered readers or authors of KnowledgeSocialNetwork. “We”, “our” and “us” refers to the staff of KnowledgeSocialNetwork. “Outside parties” refers to third party not owned or operated by KnowledgeSocialNetwork.

**INFORMATION KnowledgeSocialNetwork GATHERS AND TRACKS**

1\. KnowledgeSocialNetwork gathers two types of information about users:

Information that users provide through registration on KnowledgeSocialNetwork. These are voluntary submissions to use our site and its features:

Information KnowledgeSocialNetwork gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites and through “cookies” and IP address. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This information allows us to better tailor our content and KnowledgeSocialNetwork features to users. Under no circumstances does KnowledgeSocialNetwork divulge any information about a user to a third party.

2\. KnowledgeSocialNetwork Gathers User Information In the following processes:

Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

Users must register in order to post articles on articles although they needn’t register to visit KnowledgeSocialNetwork. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password and email address. Users can create an article draft or publish their articles or delete their articles anytime however KnowledgeSocialNetwork reserve the right to check articles and modify or remove them if they do not meet our Editorial statement.

3\. Usage tracking,

KnowledgeSocialNetwork tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. KnowledgeSocialNetwork does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

KnowledgeSocialNetwork sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for our users.

4\. Cookies We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. KnowledgeSocialNetwork uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above).

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in postings messages and networking with your favourite authors.

5\. Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

6\. USE OF INFORMATION

KnowledgeSocialNetwork uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to enable users to participate comments postings, articles reviews, share articles and follow their favourite authors.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.

KnowledgeSocialNetwork will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

7\. SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

KnowledgeSocialNetwork will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

8\. SECURITY

KnowledgeSocialNetwork operates secure data network protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users.

9\. YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by KnowledgeSocialNetwork. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. For more information please contact us click here.
